<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Eugenio Cano-Manuel Mendoza</title>
    <link>https://eugenio.sh/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Eugenio Cano-Manuel Mendoza</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 11:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eugenio.sh/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>List of favorite articles and blogs from the web</title>
      <link>https://eugenio.sh/blog/favorite-reads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenio.sh/blog/favorite-reads/</guid>
      <description>This is a living document! It&amp;rsquo;s a list of interesting articles and blog posts I&amp;rsquo;ve found on the web. Will keep updated.
 Simple Systems Have Less Downtime John Carmack on Inlined Code The Absolute Minimum Every Software Developer Absolutely, Positively Must Know About Unicode and Character Sets (No Excuses!) Jane Street Core “Notes on Time” Software disenchantment Simple Made Easy Suckless Philosophy The Majestic Monolith Use Fast Data Algorithms The Grug Brained Developer  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SQLite to optimise my electricity usage</title>
      <link>https://eugenio.sh/blog/cheapest-time-to-run-boiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 13:23:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenio.sh/blog/cheapest-time-to-run-boiler/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in the process of switching to Agile Octopus, an electricity tariff that ties the price I pay with the wholesale price, updated every 30 minutes. The reason I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking forward to switching to a tariff as dynamic as this one is to restrict my electric boiler to only run during the cheapest times of the day.
My boiler is a direct unvented cylinder. In Layman&amp;rsquo;s terms this is a big cyclinder that heats and stores water.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
